20811 Canon Ridge Lane

Cell: 909-348-4459

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/alee046

Walnut, CA 91789 Portfolio Site: www.anthonylee.xyz alee@anthonylee.xyz

### Skills

Javascript, jQuery, CSS, HTML5, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Angular, MongoDB, Express, Node, js, Bootstrap & Sass, PostgreSQL, Socket.io, Ionic Framework

## **Projects**

#### Coordinet:

Location-sharing based chat-app that allows users to communicate on their phones through a combination of custom Google map markers and a traditional chat-service. Technologies used: Socket.io, Ionic Framework, Google Maps API, Node, js, Angular, js

## ConShareto:

Worked as a team to develop a concert-tracking application with an easy to use UI using the MEN stack. My focus was on learning how to utilize our chosen API (Jambase) to pull out concert information and buildling out the front-end of the application.

#### Muse:

This app was designed to be music performance sharing service with CRUD capabilities. Users get a repo to store and share sets from Youtube, Soundcloud, or Mixcloud.

Technologies used: Ruby on Rails, Bootstrap CSS

## Hold-em (Poker Simulator):

A functional texas-hold'em simulator with complete win-check logic implemented.

Technologies used: Javascript, Bootstrap CSS, HTML

## **Employment History**

## General Assembly, Los Angeles, California **Web Development Immersive Student**

GA's WDI is a 12 week immersive web development program, during this course I spent 600+ hours learning how to build web applications.

The topics we covered through the course included the following:

- Javascript - jQuery - Ruby on Rails - Postgres and the RDBMS
- CSS & CSS Libraries (such as Bootstrap & Sass) -MVC Architechture
- API's, AJAX, and JSON - MongoDB, Express, NodeJs, and AngularJs
- Gulp task manager - BDD with Mocha / Chai, and RSPEC - Github workflow

## Lih-Jen International Elementary School, Taipei, Taiwan **Homeroom Teacher**

2014 - 2015

2015 - 2015

5th Grade homeroom teacher for a private international elementary school.

# Yama Seiki USA, Chino, CA

2014 - 2014

## **Parts Coordinator**

Account manager for a Taiwanese-based milling machine distributor.

### Education

### **BA**, Political Science

2013

University of California, Riverside, Riverside, CA